To put it in Tendo's words, I am excited.
I think something's wrong with Tsukishima's hand.
We can't win if we don't take risks.
Persistent attacks are what we do.
Full Team Synchronized Attack!
While the winds have been out a million,
the Played Parour of allies have sido möchten.
When stas with a star,
I can't see its meaning and arms.
光あれ行け 闇を滑走路にして 己の道を経験に解こう
光あれ椅子先の絶望へ 依存先の栄光を信じて
光あれ行ける理由はたった一つ 光あれ行ける理由はたった一つ
光あれ行ける理由はたった一つ もっと眩く俺は飛べる
光あれ行ける君の今日の輝きが 迷える友の明日を照らすよ
夢中時間のよう 勇気を持って 光あれ行ける
光あれ行ける
YEAH!
あ!
DIDN'T WORKED!
They need to learn that you always gotta follow up on your blocks.
Yeah, everyone going up at the same time is too risky.
Looks like that block turned out to be pretty effective.
That was really risky.
Just so you know, we'll do that again.
Ginger!
Make sure you're paying attention to your block timing.
Since you lack the height advantage, you need to make sure it's absolutely flawless.
If you feel your timing is even a slight bit off, don't hesitate to switch into a soft block.
Right! Play technique!
Woohoo!
Sorry.
No, don't worry about it.
You get a break.
How many points did they score in a row with only Ushiwaka serving the ball?
Five?
Six points, actually.
That's more than a third of what they need.
That's true, but look who's on his way out there.
Yeah!
If this works.
Kazuhito! Give us a good one!
Go for it, ma'am!
Here it comes!
Sorry.
Tendo!
Asahi!
You're not working with Kageyama, so don't just jump.
This is going to be at first tempo.
Ah!
Just two points behind.
Now that's playing with your head.
Uh-huh.
Well, that's one way to receive.
I knew my hands wouldn't reach it in time, so I used my face.
I just didn't want to get hit in the nose.
What?
You mean...
That wasn't an accident?
Well, they'd bench me if I got a nosebleed, right?
I had heard the rumors about Karasuno's first-year duo.
Then I met them one day, and the little ones started to get cocky.
I assumed he'd be like all the other small players I've dealt with,
who compensated for their short stature with excellent technique.
But I was wrong.
He shows no sign of the talent or intelligence of those other players.
But now...
I see it.
There's just something about him.
Something I can't stand.
It's not that I have any doubt that we'll win this game.
But above all, I want to defeat him.
And I want the weight of that loss to crush him.
Alright, that's the spirit!
Don't give up, you guys!
Hey, look over there!
He's doing warm-ups!
Is he going back in?
Rayon!
Alright!
Nothing can stop us now!
Oh, man.
I can taste blood.
I hope he and it does not hurt too much.
But that block follow-up?
It's a good thing we have him out there right now.
He did that last time because he saw there was no choice but to have Asahi hit it.
Lately, Karasuno's style is to have everyone go up to attack, and those who don't become decoys.
They think more about not getting blocked than what to do if they actually are.
So when they do get blocked, it's more or less out of their hands.
Although when we were in middle school, we were constantly doing drills to make sure we always followed up.
If I was the coach, I'd do the same thing.
You know?
You always want to know at least one person has your back.
It ain't easy out there.
Alright!
Nice, Sushiwaka!
Yusuke!
I'll close him out of a cross shot, so if he hits you straight, it'll go right to Daichi.
Alright, here we go.
I'm going for the straight shot!
Sorry!
That's long!
Suga!
If we choose to play it safe here, we won't make up any ground.
Are they going to do it again?
It didn't work last time.
Full team synchronized attack!
Judging from this form, I can tell he won't go for a back set.
And I've never seen him do combos with number 10 either.
So he'll probably go to Beardo in the back.
We'll do that again.
Crap, I got caught up in my train of thought.
I screwed myself over analyzing.
I never wonder if the ball is ever going to be sent to me.
It doesn't matter.
Instead, I just tell myself that I'm ready to hit.
That confidence is coming from all of us at once.
And it confuses their blockers.
Pain train!
I can tell just by looking at them.
Can't believe Sugawara was able to rebound and fully commit right after failing the first time.
Yeah, that had to be scary for him.
But he must have realized it's more important to have the balls to attack.
Ten now!
I don't give a crap if you guessed wrong!
At least stick your arms up!
Don't stand there and feel sorry for yourself!
Do something!
Yes, sir.
And here he comes!
Did you get enough beauty rest, Krapiyama?
Better watch the back of your head squirt.
Kakeyama, make us proud!
He stares like that after such a small break.
It's coming back!
It's a chance ball!
Be careful!
I got it!
Is he sending the ball from a first touch?
Damn it!
They did it!
Straight down!
Yeah, but it happened so fast I wasn't even able to catch it.
It's 9-8!
They're closing up the gap!
That little shit!
I thought a usual quick attack would have been enough to throw them off.
But then he just jumped in there all of a sudden.
That was stupid and reckless!
Come on, come on!
You're gonna have to be louder than that!
Yeah!
Here we go
Shayra Torizawa just hit double digits!
this guy has a strong serve i hope we can cut him off quick hey why isn't ada our main setter
in the first place he's way more skilled than shiribu is it depends on what you prefer as a
strong point i personally like shiribu's dependability better i know where i fall
short compared to shiribu i could probably be as good as him but i like to show off my power
i know that's not what shiratorizawa needs especially right now i just can't help myself
after all serving is the one time i get to do as i please
no touch
there's got to be something i can say to them to live their spirits
come on let's hear it it's times like this when cheering is important
let's finish this right here right hey ada give us
fire up fire up
fire up fire up fire up fire up fire up
fire up fire up fire up fire listed
Aida! One more pretty serve, pretty please!
Chad's wall!
Mushiwaka!
But he was so far from the net!
Nice! Nice block! That was a block, right?
I did tell him to soft block, but that was probably closer to a receive.
Whenever you try a move like that, you could get hit in the face.
Karasuno finally hit double digits!
Don't get so excited about your dumb luck, you would have gotten in the way of a proper receive!
Ushuaka! No way would some no-name little scrub stop you! That was a total fluke!
Maybe so.
Ushuaka's the perfect example of an ace. Everyone's eyes go straight to him. Of course he'll be stopped sometimes!
But by that little first year? It's crazy he knew to jump in from there!
Yeah!
Hey Kasuhito, play how you feel comfortable. I'll back you up.
Uh, sure!
You're up, dude!
Counting on you!
Go, Yamaguchi! Go!
Don't hold back!
Huh?
There's nothing to be afraid of out here!
I'm gonna aim for a diagonal straight right for Ushuaka.
I just have to make sure it's not a soft serve, though.
Ayato!
Get that chance ball!
Got it!
After it!
Synchronized attack!
Over here!
Come over here!
Yeah!
He touched the net! Lucky us!
It's not just luck alone.
Huh?
If Garasuno keeps on pushing them, it's only natural that they are going to push back.
Damn it!
Ah! That's all you?
Ushuaka!
Slowly, guys. Now ready?
And...
Go!
We put up so many walls, but we're still having trouble stopping him!
I got it!
I didn't time that right!
Yeah!
All right! We caught him!
Hey, that was too high for you, right?
I'll fix it.
Oh, um, okay.
It's your first time teaming up today, and you guys pulled off a quick attack already?
Just like last time, Tanashi!
It's going long!
It's out!
Ah!
Sorry!
I didn't call it fast enough!
No, it's...
I just...
YAMAKUSHI!
Nice one!
Thanks!
Time!
What's the matter, Goshiki?
You've got to beat yourself up.
Remember, you're a talented player.
YAMAKUSHI!
Oh...
Thanks.
We'll stop the next one.
Right!
He doesn't lie or exaggerate.
And his words don't have any hidden meanings.
He just says it how it is.
From one ace to another.
They've turned it around!
That's three points in a row!
If they're able to keep this up, they might just pull off a miracle and win this thing!
Get it!
Get it, Karasuno!
Not bad!
Sweet!
That was perfect!
Did you see that?
What a savage angle!
They snuck it through before they finished setting up the block.
I bet that felt pretty good for him after his mistake with that last receive.
You did really good out there!
Now leave the rest to me!
But you're gonna be switching out with Noya soon yourself.
Go Ski!
Keep a level head!
I already know that!
Here we go!
Bring it!
Damn it!
I thought number eight was supposed to be the impulsive one.
Goshki is the only first year we have in our starting line-up.
For a good reason.
Noya!
It looks like they've got Karasuno cornered.
And Four Eyes isn't here to save the day.
I don't know if they can survive this match point.
Nice receive!
Synchronized attack!
Yeah!
Isn't the guy who just received for you to score?
It's a deuce.
Logically, they should be running out of stamina by now.
Yet they send the whole team to attack?
Using their strength in numbers.
Even I have to admit it's a pretty effective offense against us.
Hey Coach!
I'm the best there is when it comes to receives!
I also have great jumping power and I'm confident in my attacks as well!
That may be true, but you do lack height.
Sorry kid.
So I can't compete because I'm short?
I'm not going to compete because I'm short?
No!
No. What I want is...
If we don't break through soon, then Karasuno is in for some real trouble.
Strength and concentration could give out at any moment. Stay focused, guys.
Come on, we have to stop that ball from hitting the floor in any way we possibly can.
Tai Chi, you got this, bro!
It's too short!
Aiming for the edge of the net is such a cheap trick.
Goshki, I'm on it!
Well, don't just stand there! Go get it!
Kageyama, get last!
Okay, that's your chance!
Get it! Kill it!
They forced our center to get that one.
Ushiwaka!
If we mess this timing up, it's over. Just don't panic.
And... go!
I wanna find a way to fight.
Even if I am small.
No, what I want is...
Simple, raw strength which would allow even me to overwhelm all my opponents.
Whoa, he saved it!
Damn it! It's taking everything we've got just to send it back!
It's clear. Both sides are low on stamina and are fighting for control.
Neither wants to lose this rally.
Just don't drop the ball, boys!
It hasn't fallen yet!
We still have a chance!
Please just get it!
This is it!
Shut up already!
WE ARE THE STRONGER TEAM!
Yes!
Yeah!
Y-yos!
And ch deposits
hatteؤlamuts
You see why not?
Who see why not miss it?
One more point!
This is not good. That was a real shot to morale. And we're out of timeouts.
Don't you hang your heads! Stop it!
Volleyball is a sport where you always have to look up!
Yaachii!
力少なくじゃまだ届かずしまい
ギリギリで繋いで放つ願い
ただ人やタイミングには恵まれて
へこたれずにいられてる
真っ向から勝負したい
迷ってもじっと堪えとこう
The chance is there
Oh, oh, oh
It's for you, it's for you
We're just gonna sing it
We're just gonna see tomorrow
It's for you, it's for you
Now we're not even ready
We're fast
風の色目に染みる
ゆとりをもって
悟り詰め込んで
誇り高く生きたい
No doubt
あとは君次第です
全部君次第
きっと甘い甘いと言われても
違うよ違うとけなされたって
あとは君次第
迷うんじゃない
ララララララララ
君次第
バイ
Girl, you okay?
i'm fine
i usually
don't have to run long distances
Alright, Yachi's back
Time for the counter-attack
Next haikyuu
Fools for Volleyball